knowing-jesus.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document  
outlines the types of personal information we receive and  
collect when you use (website/company name), as well as some  
of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this  
will help you make an informed decision about sharing  
personal information with us.

**www.knowing-jesus.com**  strives to maintain the highest  
standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our  
operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our  
customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our  
website.

### Personal Information

**www.knowing-jesus.com**  collects personally identifiable  
information from the visitors to our website only on a  
voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a  
voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email  
address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information  
from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign  
up to join our email list or request some other service or  
information from us. The information collected is internally  
reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify  
our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in  
our files. If we make material changes in the collection of  
personally identifiable information we will inform you by  
placing a notice on our site. Personal information received  
from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and  
will not be sold or provided to third parties.

### Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online  
experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to  
your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to  
enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of  
a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to  
a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites  
pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie  
enables  **www.knowing-jesus.com  **to recall your specific  
information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by  
modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to  
decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the  
interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor  
your journey around a single website or collection of sites.  
They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used  
by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.  
They may be used in association with cookies to understand  
how visitors interact with the pages and content on the  
pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and  
web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web  
site to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an  
advertisement. No personally identifiable information you  
give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so  
they cannot personally identify you with that information on  
our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google,  
which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the  
DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based  
on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You  
may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
[  
Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify  
you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be  
used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions  
shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so  
choose.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to  
children under the age of 13. We operate our site in  
compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection  
Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal  
information from anyone under 13 years of age.

### Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is  
not personally identifiable. We use this information, which  
does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to  
administer the site, to track users’ movements around the  
site and to gather demographic information about our user  
base as a whole. The information collected is used solely  
for internal review and not shared with other organizations  
for commercial purposes.

### Release of Information

If  **www.knowing-jesus.com  **is sold, the information we have  
obtained from you through your voluntary participation in  
our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale  
in order that the service being provided to you may  
continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our  
website of that change in control and practices, and we will  
make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors  
any opt-out requests you might make of us.

### How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our  
commitment to protect your personal information. If you have  
submitted personal information through our website and would  
like that information deleted from our records or would like  
to update or correct that information, please click on this  
link and/or use our Contact Us page.

### Google for search

The search box on this web site (“Search Box”) is powered by Google Inc (“Google”). You acknowledge and agree that Google’s privacy policy (located at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.

### Updates and Effective Date

**www.knowing-jesus.com  **reserves the right to make changes in  
this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy  
practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy  
practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy  
policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy  
so that you will know what information we collect and how we  
use it.

### To EU Users:

Please read our disclosure notice as part of our compliance to the EU user consent policy:

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. For more information on how Google uses data when you use our partner’ sites or apps, visit this link: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/>

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to www.knowing-Jesus.com Privacy  
Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use  
this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy  
policy.
